Finding aid for WUOM Records, 1914-1982
Bentley Historical Library
- Audio Material, 1930s-1970s
  - Sound Reels (10.5 inch)
    - U-M Conferences and Lectures
      - Department of English
        - Robert Bly ([R209B]), 1963 November 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-85-1-1]; (English Department Reading, Broadcast 1-6-64; Robert Bly reads "Driving to Town Late to Mail A Letter", "Unanswered Letters", "In A Train" ,"The Spring Rides Down", "Suffocation", Poem about Kennedy Administration, "Taking the Hands", poem about being in love in Minnesota, music, the WPA bridge, about Bly's horse, Issa poems; five minute break begins at 28:00, question and answer session, "Gentleman Without Any Company", "Questions", "Depression", "Looking Backward", "Avoidance", "Roving the Ground.")
        - "Reaching the Unreached: English in Every Classroom" [speech] / Daniel Fader--recorded [part of Toward the Better Teaching of High School English Conference], broadcast Lecture Hour, August 30, 1965, August 2, 1965; [R210B] (Box 25)
        - Symposium on the Contemporary English Novel ([R211B]), 1959 March 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-86-1-1]; (English Department Lecture and Panel Discussion. Panelists are: Marvin Felheim, James Gindin, and Donald Hall.)
        - "Toys in the Attic" Lillian Hellman ([R212B]), 1960 April 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 25)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-87-1-1]; (Lillian Hellman speaking on her play "Toys in the Attic.")
      - Draft Teach-In
        - "The Draft and the University" ([R213B]), 1968 March 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-88-1-1]; (Draft Teach-In and panel discussion about the implications of the draft and University students. Panelists and speakers are: James Lafferty, Paul Rupert, James Jones, and William Sloan Coffin; introduced by William Gamson. (broadcast on Lecture Hour June 1, 1968))
        - "The Rights and Responsibilities of Dissent in a Free Society" Herbert [Kelman] ([R214B]), 1968 March 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-89-1-1]; (Draft Teach In; with Terry Sandalow; Spencer Parsons; Bob Harris; William Sloane Coffin.)
      - Ecumenical Campus Center/First Presbyterian Church. Church and Society Committee
        - "Campus Unrest" [panel discussion] ([R215B]), 1970 July 07; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-90-1-1]; (Ecumenical Campus Center/First Presbyterian Church. Church and Society Committee. Paul R. Dotson; Robben W. Fleming; Gardner Ackley; Joseph N. Payne; Gordon J. Van Wylen; Stephen J. Tonsor; Terence N. Tice; Gilbert E. Bursley. excerpts broadcast Commentary July 9, 16, 23, 30, 1970,)
      - Esquire Symposium (Department of English Annual Writer's Conference), 3 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips
        - Esquire Panel: "The Role of the Writer in America" ([R216B]), 1961 October 27-28 (Box 26)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-91-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 3; Esquire Symposium (Department of English Annual Writer's Conference) Nelson Algren; Gore Vidal; William Styron; Vance Bourjaily; introduced by Allen Seager, Arnold Gingrich.)
        - Esquire Panel: "The Role of the Writer in America" ([R217B]), 1961 October 27-28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-91-2-1]; (Tape 2 of 3; Esquire Symposium (Department of English Annual Writer's Conference) Nelson Algren; Gore Vidal; William Styron; Vance Bourjaily; introduced by Allen Seager, Arnold Gingrich.)
        - Esquire Panel: "The Role of the Writer in America" ([R218B]), 1961 October 27-28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Reel 3, Part 1], [8738-SR-91-3-1]; (Tape 3 of 3; Esquire Symposium (Department of English Annual Writer's Conference) Nelson Algren; Gore Vidal; William Styron; Vance Bourjaily; introduced by Allen Seager, Arnold Gingrich.)
      - [Irving Howe Symposium]
        - "Radical Resistance: Success or Suicide?" ([R219B]), 1968 January 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-92-1-1]; (Howe Symposium / Barry Bluestone; Tom Maher; Irving Howe; John Bishop. (broadcast Lecture Hour March 16, 1968))
      - Hopwood Ceremonies
        - Hopwood Ceremonies Malcolm Cowley; introduced by Arno Bader([R220B]), 1957; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-1-1]; (Malcolm Cowley speaking on the "Beginning Writer and the University." (broadcast May 1957))
        - Hopwood Ceremonies John Ciardi ("The Silences of the Poem"); introduced by Arno Bader ([R221B]), 1958; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-2-1]; (John Ciardi discusses technical aspects of poetry; final ten minutes is an award ceremony. (broadcast Lecture Hour June 14, 1958))
        - Hopwood Ceremonies Howard Nemerov; introduced by Allen Seager ([R222B]), 1959 May 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-3-1]; (Howard Nemerov discussing "The Swaying Form: A Problem in Poetry." broadcast Lecture Hour [1959])
        - Hopwood Ceremonies Saul Bellow ([R223B]), 1961 June 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-4-1]; (Broadcast Lecture Hour June 20, 1961; Hopwood Ceremonies lecture with Saul Bellow discussing writing, broadcast Lecture Hour June 20, 1961)
        - Hopwood Ceremonies Mark Schorer; introduced by Arno Bader ([R224B]), 1962 May 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-5-1]; (Mark Schorer discussing "The Burdens of Biography." rebroadcast Lecture Hour August 23, 1962)
        - Hopwood Ceremonies Arthur Miller ("Recognition"); introduced by Arno Bader ([R225B]), 1963 May 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-6-1]; (Broadcast Lecture Hour; June 05 1963; Re-broadcast December 02, 1963. Arthur Miller's topic for this lecture is "On Recognition.")
        - Hopwood Ceremonies Alfred Kazin ("Autobiography As Narrative"); introduced by Arno Bader ([R226B]), 1964 May 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-7-1]; (Alfred Kazin speaking on the topic "Autobiography As Narrative." Broadcast Lecture Hour May 9, 1964.)
        - Hopwood Ceremonies Donald Davie ("Sincerity and Poetry"); introduced by Arno Bader ([R227B]), 1965 April 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-8-1]; (Donald Davie speaking on the topic "Sincerity and Poetry.")
        - Hopwood Ceremonies Stephen Spender ([R228B]), 1982 April 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-9-1]; (Broadcast July 28, 1982; Stephen Spender speaking on an unlisted topic.)
        - Hopwood Ceremonies Kenneth Rexroth with Kyoto ([R229B]), 1979 January 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 26)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-10-1]; (Tape was found to be blank during digital transfer.)
        - Hopwood Ceremonies John Ciardi, et al. ([R230B]), 1981 April 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-11-1]; (Tape was found to be blank during digital transfer.)
        - Hopwood Ceremony with John Ciardi, Kennedy and Donnely. ([R231B]), 1981 April 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-93-12-1]; (Tape was found to be blank during digital transfer.)
      - Institute for Continuing Legal Education
        - Student Protest and the Law Conference: Welcome Address / Robben W. Fleming; "Dimensions of Legitimate Student Dissent" ([R232B]), 1969 May 16-17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-94-1-1]; (Welcome address by Robert Fleming during the Student Protest and the Law Conference in 1969. Then a panel discussion with Paul D. Carrington, moderator; Richard L. Cates; Marvin L. Niehuss; Robert N. Knause; Institute for Continuing Legal Ed.)
      - Michigan Union Cultural Affairs Committee
        - Robert Frost; introduced by Donald Hall ([R233B]), 1962 April 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-95-1-1]; (Recorded April 02, 1962, Broadcast on Lecture Hour May 2, 1962, rebroadcast December 24, 1971. Lecture-reading by poet Robert Frost in Ann Arbor under the auspices of the Cultural Affairs Committee of the Michigan Union.)
      - New Mobilization Committee; Friends of the White Panthers
        - Jane Fonda; ([R234B]), 1971 February 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-96-1-1]; (Broadcast February 9, 1971, Recorded December 1, 1970 New Mobilization Committee; Friends of the White Panthers.)
      - Office of Religious Affairs
        - "Symbol and Myth: The Language of Religion" / Paul Tillich ([R235B), 1960 November 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-97-1-1]; (Recorded November 13, 1960, broadcast Lecture Hour January 21, 1961,rebroadcast Lecture Hour June 19, 1961.)
        - "An Understanding of Black Power" / Stokley Carmichael ([R236B]), 1966 September 27; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-98-1-1]; (Tape was found to be blank during digital transfer. Stokley Carmichael lecturing on the topic of "An Understanding of Black Power.")
      - Repression Teach-In ((sponsor: Ann Arbor Committee on Repression
        - Repression Teach-In: Jerry Rubin; Arthur Kinoy; Edward Crowther; et al. ([R237B]), 1970 January 30; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-99-1-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 3; Repression Teach-In sponsored by the Ann Arbor Committee on Repression held at the University of Michigan in January 1970, introduced by Gary Bluestone.)
          - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-99-1-1-2]; (Tape 2 of 3; Repression Teach-In sponsored by the Ann Arbor Committee on Repression held at the University of Michigan in January 1970, introduced by Gary Bluestone.)
          - [Reel 3, Part 1], [8738-SR-99-1-1-3]; (Tape 3 of 3; Repression Teach-In sponsored by the Ann Arbor Committee on Repression held at the University of Michigan in January 1970, introduced by Gary Bluestone.)
      - Teach-In on the Environment (sponsors: ENACT; New Mobilization Committee)
        - "Citizen Action" / Ralph Nader ([R240B]), 1970 March 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-100-1-1]; (Recorded March 14, 1970, Broadcast Lecture Hour, May 16, 1970; Ralph Nader, consumer protection expert, speaks at the Hill Auditorium as part of the Teach-In on the Environment at the University of Michigan in mid-march, sponsored by ENACT.)
        - [War and the Environment] ([R241B]), 1970 March 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-101-1-1]; (Edited March 25, 1970; broadcast Lecture Hour May 23, 1970; War and the Environment panel as part of the Teach-In on the Environment at the University of Michigan in mid-march, sponsored by ENACT. Panelists include: Kenneth Boulding, Anatol Rapoport, Douglas Fulton, Irwin Goldstein, and David Gordon.)
      - Unidentified Sponsorship
        - Katherine Anne Porter ([R242B]), 1954 March 04; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-102-1-1]; (Reads: "Flowering Judas" and an unknown poem.)
        - G.B. Harrison ([R243B]), 1954 April 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-103-1-1]; (Reading of English Poetry reads Shakespeare, John Donne, John Milton, William Blake, Francis Thompson, Gerard Manley Hopkins.)
        - Bennett Weaver ([R244B]), 1955 March 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-104-1-1]; (Reads Robert Frost, Robert Peter Tristram Coffin, discusses rhythm and meter, William Cullen Bryant.)
        - E.E. Cummings ([R245B]), 1957 March 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 27)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-105-1-1]; (Poetry reading and lecture by E.E. Cummings.)
        - Robert Graves; introduced by Norman Nelson ([R246B]), 1958 February 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-106-1-1]; (Poetry reading and lecture by Robert Graves.)
        - E.E. Cummings; introduced by Frank Cople ([R247B]), 1960 May 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-107-1-1]; (Poetry reading and lecture by E.E. Cummings.)
        - Louis Simpson ([R248B]), 1966 March 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-108-1-1]; (Louis Simpson, discusses and reads his work during the creative arts festival; reads: "Carentan O Carentan", "Summer Storm", "The Battle", "Early in the Morning", "To the Western World", "In California", "Summer Morning", "Birch", "A Story About Chicken Soup", "The Inner Part", "On the Lawn at the Villa", "Walt Whitman at Bear Mountain", "Black Kettle Raises the Stars and Stripes", "Outward", "After Midnight", "American Dreams", "Moonlight on a Veranda", "Returning", "Why Are You Walking?", "The Shadow Hunter", "Sacred Objects.")
        - Lemuel Johnson ([R249B]), 1978 February 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-109-1-1]; (Tape was found to be blank during digital transfer.)
        - Joseph Brodsky ([R250B]), 1979 March 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-110-1-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 2; Tape was found to be blank during digital transfer.)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-110-1-1-2]; mp3 file; (Tape 2 of 2; Tape was found to be blank during digital transfer.)
        - Malcolm X ([R252B]), 1963 October 21, [22?]; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-111-1-1]; (Recording of a Malcolm X speech.)
      - University Activities Center (UAC)
        - "Exploration of the Moods of Dissent: A Dialogue with the President" / Robben W. Fleming, et al. ([R253B-R254B]), 1968 March 18; 2 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-112-1-1-1]; (Tape 1 of 2; Panel members: Roy Ashmole; Sam Sherman; Mark Levin; Prof. Knausse; Dr. J. Minzey.)
          - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-112-1-1-2]; (Tape 2 of 2; Panel members: Roy Ashmole; Sam Sherman; Mark Levin; Prof. Knausse; Dr. J. Minzey.)
        - "Poets on the War in Vietnam" ([R255B-R256B]), 1966 October 02-03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1], [8738-SR-113-1-1-1]; (Poetry Read-In - Robert Bly; Will Geer; W.D. Snodgrass; John Woods; Tim Reynolds; Jerry Badanes; Donald Hall; Galway Kinnell.)
          - [Reel 2, Part 1], [8738-SR-113-1-1-2]; (Poetry Read-In - Robert Bly; Will Geer; W.D. Snodgrass; John Woods; Tim Reynolds; Jerry Badanes; Donald Hall; Galway Kinnell.)
        - "The Recent Past and the Immediate Future" [speech and question/answer session]) / Benjamin Spock ([R257B]), 1969 February 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-114-1-1]; (Topic: war resistance and pacifism; recorded February 2, 1969, broadcast Lecture Hour April 26, 1969; Prof Kaufman of Philosophy Dept; Prof Faingold School of Public Health; Gregory Finger Of Massachusetts Legal Defense Committee after address.)
      - University of Michigan Afro-American Retreat
        - Afro-American Retreat [Scholarship for Long-term Change] ([R258B]), 1969 May 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-115-1-1]; (Panel discussion at the University of Michigan Afro-American Retreat; "Scholarship for Long-term Change," with Ivanhoe Donaldson, Ronald Harris, Lonnie Peek, Louis Lomax.)
      - University of Michigan Centennial of Lincoln's Emancipation Proclamation
        - Centennial of Lincoln's Emancipation Proclamation/ Langston Hughes ([R259B]), 1963 January 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 28)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-116-1-1]; (Recorded January 8, 1963; Broadcast March 9, 1963; Lecture Hour broadcast on Langston Hughes. Introduction by Joe Lee Davis; used commentary at his death May 22, 1967.)
      - University of Michigan Senate
        - UM Senate Assembly Meeting ([R260B]), 1982 February 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-117-1-1]; mp3 file; (Vice President Frye presents the Five-Year Plan at the UM Senate Assembly Meeting. Tape was found to be blank during digital transfer.)
        - Robben W. Fleming ([R261B]), 1970 April 13; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-118-1-1]; (UM Senate; Report on Black Action Movement and actions taken in response to BAM demands.)
      - Vietnam Teach-In
        - [Personal Views Concerning Vietnam War] Robben W. Fleming ([R262B]), 1969 October 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-119-1-1]; (Recorded September 19, 1969 Vietnam Teach-In; broadcast Special of the Week September 20, 1969 (Incomplete)); Rebroadcast: October 15, 1969. Robben W. Fleming discusses Personal Views Concerning Vietnam War during Vietnam Teach-In. Intro by Rhoads Murphey; Rennie Davis.)
        - [Response to Fleming; Report on visit to Hanoi] / Rennie Davis ([R263B]), 1969 October 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-120-1-1]; (Vietnam Teach-In; Rennie Davis, graduate of Michigan and one of the Chicago eight, speaks in response to President Fleming's opposition to the war during the Vietnam Teach-In.)
      - War Moratorium (sponsor: New Mobilization to End the War)
        - Rally at Michigan Stadium [live broadcast] / Rennie Davis ([R264B-R265B]), 1969 October 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Part 1], [8738-SR-121-1-1-1]; (War Moratorium: includes excerpts from speeches made at other Moratorium sessions; Inserts: Fleming; Ac[text illegible], Arvley, Ginsburg.)
        - Allen Ginsberg Speech ([R265B]), 1969 October 15 (Box 29)
          - [Part 2], [8738-SR-121-1-1-2]; (Sponsored by Friends of Ann Arbor Argus: John Sinclair Speech during War Moratorium.)
    - U-M History
      - History Archives [oral history interviews] original recording 1965-1966
        - History Archives Reel #1: Leo Sharfman; Charles Sink; Ralph Sawyer; Stanley Dodge ([R266B-R272B]), 1965 August, September; 1966; 7 Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          (see participant list below] Summaries of interviews available.)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1-1], [8738-SR-122-1-1-1]; (U-M History July 15, 1966; History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Guests: I. Leo Sharfman and Charles Sink.)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1-2], [8738-SR-122-1-1-2]; (U-M History 7/15/1966; History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966; Guests: Ralph Sawyer, Physics.)
          - [Reel 1, Part 1-3], [8738-SR-122-1-1-3]; (U-M History 7/15/1966; History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966; Guests: Ralph Sawyer,Physics; Stanley Dodge; Geography.)
        - History Archives Reel #2: George Carrothers; Harrison Randall; Preston Slosson; Hazel Losh ([R267B]), 1965 July, August, December; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Ree1 2 Part 1-1], [8738-SR-122-2-1-1]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Guests: George Carrothers, Education; Harrison Randall, Physics.)
          - [Reel 2, Part 1-2], [8738-SR-122-2-1-2]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Guests: Harrison Randall, Physics; Preston Slosson, History; Hazel Losh, Astronomy.)
        - History Archives Reel #3: Margaret Tracy; Henry Frieze Vaughn; Wells I. Bennett ([R268B]), 1965, August, September, October; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Reel 3, Part 1-1], [8738-SR-122-3-1-1]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Guests: Margaret Tracy,first woman professor of the Business School; Henry Frieze Vaughn, Dean of the School of Public Health.)
          - [Reel 3, Part 1-2], [8738-SR-122-3-1-2]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Guests: Henry Henry Frieze Vaughn; first dean of Public Health School; son of Victor Vaughn; Wells I. Bennett, Dean of Architecture.)
        - History Archives Reel #4: Henry Carter Adams II; Arthur Dearth Moore; Arthur Denham ([R269B]), 1965 September; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Reel 4, Part 1-1], [8738-SR-122-4-1-1]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Henry Carter Adams II, Naval Architecture; Arthur Dearth Moore, Engineering.)
          - [Reel 4, Part 1-2], [8738-SR-122-4-1-2]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Arthur Dearth Moore, Engineering; Arthur Denham, School of Social Work.)
        - History Archives Reel #5: Clarence Cook Little; Samuel Dana; William Trow; Ruel Churchill ([R270B]), 1965 September, December, 1966 January; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Reel 5, Part 1-1], [8738-SR-122-5-1-1]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Guests: Clarence Cook Little, President; Samuel Dana, School of Natural Resources.)
          - [Reel 5, Part 1-1], [8738-SR-122-5-1-2]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Guests William Trow, Education and Psychology; Ruel Churchill, Math.)
        - History Archives Reel #6: Philip Bursley; E. Blythe Stason; Roscoe Bonnisteel; Charles Kennedy ([R271B]), 1965 July, September, December; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Reel 6, Part 1-1], [8738-SR-122-6-1-1]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Phili Bursley, Romance Languages, E. Blythe Stason, Dean of the Law School and Provost of the University.)
          - [Reel 6, Part 1-2], [8738-SR-122-6-1-2]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966. Roscoe Bonnisteel, Law Student, Regent of the University; Charles Kennedy, Medical Student, Regent of the University.)
        - History Archives Reel #7: Helen Hebelar; William Paton; Arthur Furstenberg ([R272B]), 1965 September, December; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)
          - [Reel 7, Part 1-1], [8738-SR-122-7-1-1]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966; Helen Hebelar, Nurse at University Hospital; William Paton, accounting, Dean of Business Administration.)
          - [Reel 7, Part 1-2], [8738-SR-122-7-1-2]; (U-M History 7/15/1966, History Archives was a series of oral history broadcasts from 1965 to 1966; William Paton, Accounting, Dean of Business Administration; Arthur Furstenberg, Medical Dean.)
    - U-M Sesquicentennial Celebration
      - $55 Million Dollar Campaign: Speeches (Victory Dinner) ([R273B-R274B- R275B]), 1967 December 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 10.5 inch, 7 1/2 ips (Box 29)